Are you afraid that an illness could wipe out your years
of savings?
Anyone would break into a sweat after seeing hospital bills worth lakhs.
But today I will tell you
how you can protect your entire deposit with just a few rupees premium.
In today's video we will learn
how to get health insurance from mobile in 2 minutes.  So first of all you have to
go to Play Store in your mobile and from here
you have to download an app whose name is
PhonePe, so let me show it here,
you have to search by writing PhonePe here
and see, it will come, then you have to install it from here, it is
already installed in my mobile,
so let me open it.
You can also login by entering your mobile number.
As soon as you log in,
such an interface will appear.  You have to go down and
see here Insurance
by Car Health Life is visible, here the option of More is
visible, so click on it
and see here
Health Insurance is visible, so click on it,
after clicking see whether you
want to do it for yourself or for both yourself and your wife
or for your child or for your
parents, you
can choose as per your convenience.  So let
me just do mine.  So I have chosen this and am
clicking on myself.
After that, see the
find plan visible below.  So you have to click on this.
Click and you will see that here it is visible
Enter Age of All Members.  So my age is
29.  So let me fill it up here.
Then here it is asking to cut
current address pin code.  So here you have to
enter the pin code.
Then here it is saying that does any member have any
existing disease.  Do any of the
members have any of these diseases
like diabetes, high BP, heart disease,
PTC, so I don't have it, so
I am clicking on no here.  Here
you have to enter the PIN code.
After filling up everything,
you have to tick here and
click on Pay View Plan here.
See, as soon as you click on View Plan, the
interface will open here
and see here there are many companies
which provide health insurance.  Like
ICICI LBRD Aditya Birla Capital Superstar
Care Health there are many companies and
you can see above that it is written here that the
policy term is one year,
if you want to make it two years then you can
choose two years.  If you want to do three years of tax then you can
choose this 3 years.
Let me be one year old.
Then here the cover
amount shown is Rs 10 lakh.  If you want more, if you
want to increase it to Rs 15 lakh, then see, the
insurance of the company will become higher.
Look, it has become ₹79.  Look, I had deposited Rs 10 lakh, but
here it is showing Rs 552.  So
let me do it for only Rs 10 lakh and there are
many companies here.  So let me
take ICICI LBRD from here,
see here the option is visible,
select and here see
plan benefit is visible, so by clicking on view all
you can see what
facilities you will get.  Click on View All here.
What will you get under your health insurance?  All these
things are given here and if you do
not understand then you can understand it by using Google Translate or AI
in Hindi
and after that you have to come back from here
and see the select
option is visible here.  You have to click on this.
After clicking on this, see
here it is visible that the monthly
installment is 555 and if you make yearly payment
then ₹380 will be deducted per month at ₹32.  So it will cost ₹32 per month.
So I don't have to do it yearly.  I want to do
monthly.  So I'm doing monthly.
After that, see, the proceed option
is visible here.  You have to click on this.
After clicking, see that more
options are coming here like rider
benefit.  If you want some more
benefits here, you can add them.  Here, let's say
I want to add Claim Protector.
So see, my ₹28 has increased.
My payment has increased by ₹8.
And you want to cover benefit OPD.
If you want to do this then see this and
my ₹12 has increased.  Health checkup is here.
If you want to add this, see
my ₹700 has become ₹88.  So you
can see according to your own how much money you have,
you can take your benefit accordingly
and after that see below, if you do
not want to choose any option then here you will
see the option of skip, you have to click on it,
after clicking on skip, see here
you have to enter your name in first name,
first name last name, then here date of
birth, then here you have to enter your head weight, how much is your
height, all this, then
see the policy holder details here, here
you have to enter the PAN number, email ID,
here you have to fill up the mobile number.
Then here in your current address
line, you have to
fill up your address in both of them.  Here
is your pin code.  Then
if you want to add someone's name as nominee, you can do so here.
Then
what is your relationship with the nominee name nominee?  What
is your relationship with the nominee?  They can select from here.
What is your relationship with the nominee?  They
can select.  By clicking here.
Then you have to enter the name of the nominee here.  Then
enter the date of birth of the nominee and
click on continue here.  So let me
fill everything up.
After filling up everything, see here
below you will see the option of Continue.
So you have to click on this.
After clicking, see the option is
visible here.  Have any persistent
disease.  Do you already have any disease
like diabetes, high BP, heart
disease, HIV, genetics? I don't have any,
so I am clicking on no.
Then here it is visible that has any medical
history.  Were you hospitalized anywhere five days
ago?  Have
you been treated for anything?  then no.  Then
here you can get conditionally issued and declined
health life insurance.  So no, I am saying no here.
Then smoke consume
alcohol or any tobacco products.  So I don't do any
intoxicants here.  So I am
clicking on no.  Clicked on no in all four.
After that, see, the
option of apply is visible below here.  So you have to
click on this.
After clicking, see that everything has been
filled up for you here.  If you
feel that there is something missing or wrong in it,
then you can correct it by clicking on edit here.
So let me be all
right.  After that, see the terms
and conditions visible below.  So you have to
select this.  Have to tick it.
After that, see the
continue option visible here.  You have to click on this.
Click here and see what is visible here.
So by clicking on Pay, just like you do on Phone Pay,
anyone has to enter their UPI PIN
number and make the payment.  As soon as you
make the payment, the document will be sent to the
email ID you have filled up
and your health
insurance will be done.  So I just wanted to
give you a demo.  I had to tell you how it is done.  That is the
process I have told you.
If you like the video then like
and subscribe to the channel.